Thanh Khac

Ruby on Rails Developer

kingkid162@gmail.com

Summary

Experienced Ruby On Rail Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Express.js, Unity3D, SQL, Node.js, and Linux. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Information Systems from University of Engineering and Technology, Ha Noi.

Experience

Ruby On Rail Developer at Rakuna

February 2017 - Present (2 months)

- Integrated Sendgrid Webhooks to show tracking mailer.
- Do background jobs with Sidekiq.
- Do BDD and TDD, and maintaining all the RSpec test case.
- Do continuous integration (wercker.com).
- Improved communication skills.

Unity Game Developer at SG Media

February 2016 - October 2016 (9 months)

Education

University of Engineering and Technology, Ha Noi

Bachelor's degree, Information Systems, 2013 - 2017

CoderSchool

Ruby on Rails, 2016 - 2016

Skills & Expertise

JavaScript

Unity3D

Ruby on Rails

Programming

Node.js

Ruby

MongoDB

Java

Behavior-Driven Development (BDD)

Express.js

Algorithms

Linux

SQL

C#

Organizations

GDG Ha Noi

November 2015 to Present

CoderSchool

Alumi

December 2016 to Present

Languages

English

(Limited working proficiency)

Vietnamese

(Native or bilingual proficiency)

Thanh Khac

Ruby on Rails Developer

kingkid162@gmail.com



Contact Thanh on LinkedIn